翻譯：安sim 圈圈 TanKnoX 茶炒栗子
翻譯：青椒 al_ice 兮之 hannah愛天津
時間軸：若林  校對：愛吃屎的魚
后期：zzzyusa  總監：愛吃屎的魚
天使圣器  骸骨之城
我知道
Yeah, no, I know,
只要你開口  我都會去辦的
but when you tell me to do something, i'm gonna do it,
所以我正在給他寫郵件
so I'm e-mailing him right now.
我不知道他要多久才回來
Well, I don't know how quick he's gonna get back
你也知道  他不經常查收郵件
'cause you know sometimes he doesn't check, so...
沒錯  誦詩會之后  我不會直接回家
Yeah, and after the poetry reading, I'm not going home.
那天是我生日  我想去夜店狂歡一下
I mean, it's my birthday, so I want to go to a club.
不  西蒙  我才不會騙她
No, Simon, I'm not gonna lie to her.
我只是不告訴她而已
I'm just not gonna tell her.
我先去把卡車停好
Let me go park the truck.
-待會兒見  -好的
- See you later, all right? - Okay.
蘿西婭  最近好嗎
Hi, Dorothea, how are you?
我是挺好的  謝謝關心
I'm good, thanks for asking.
我打算打個電話  再要幾張票
So I'll just call, I guess, and get extra tickets.
對  當然
Yeah, sure.
-我馬上就辦  -你在呢
- I'll do it right now. - Hey, you.
是西蒙
Simon.
對啊
Yeah.
-你好  西蒙  -沒錯
- Hi, Simon. - Yeah.
他說  "打給我"
He says, "Call me."
對  對  她剛到家
Yeah, yeah, she just got home.
她肯定能聽到你  她就在我旁邊
I'm sure she can hear you, she's standing right here.
-你好  盧克  -你好嗎  克萊莉
- Hey, Luke. - How's it going, Clary?
不  我很快換好衣服
No, I'll get dressed quick.
要咖啡嗎
Do you want some coffee?
再聊下去  我會遲到的
If we keep talking, I'm gonna be late.
好  那里見  拜拜
Yeah, I'll meet you there. Bye.
剛剛你是不是用了...
Did you just use the...
你感覺怎么樣
How are you feeling?
挺好的  怎么了
Fine, why?
你保證今晚直接回家
You make sure you come straight home tonight.
媽媽  拜托  只是個誦詩會而已
Mom, come on. Just a poetry reading.
我知道
I know.
再見
Bye.
你得和她談談  喬瑟琳
You need to talk to her, Jocelyn.
她還沒準備好  至少現在沒有
She's not ready, not yet.
不  她準備好了
Yes, she is.
是你沒準備好
You're not.
對了  謝謝你能過來
By the way, thanks for doing this.
他的詩歌對他意義重大
His poetry means a lot to him.
朋友就該相互支持嘛
That's what friends are for.
"來吧"
"Come
"我體內強大的偽神主啊"
"My faux juggernaut
"我腰間的邪惡"
"My nefarious loins
"每一次的噴涌"
"Slather
"都覆蓋著厚厚枯涸的熱情"
"Every protuberance with arid zeal
"苦痛"
"Agony
"折磨"
"Torment"
我聽不下去了  你要不要再來杯咖啡
I can't listen to this. You want another coffee?
好啊
Yeah.
"如同片片嬌弱的番紅花瓣囈語著死亡"
"Like tiny crocus petals whisper death"
卡布奇諾和意式濃咖啡
Cappuccino and espresso.
"大地溺死在雨中"
"Rain drowns the earth
"顫栗的微風穿過病態的繡帷"
"Shivering breezes weave through a morbid tapestry
"彌漫著潰爛的氣息"
"Of festering disease
"腫脹折磨著我"
"Turgid is my torment"
給你
There you go.
謝謝
Thank you.
"大地溺死在雨中..."
"Rain drowns the earth..."
那邊的金發美女在對你拋媚眼
That blonde girl over there was totally flirting with you.
約她出去
Ask her out.
-不  那可不行  -為什么
- Nah, it wouldn't be fair. - Why?
因為...
Well, because...
因為我心里有別人了
because I'm saving myself for someone else.
誰
Who?
"...折磨著我"
"...Is my torment."
謝謝  非常感謝
Thank you, thank you very much.
謝謝
Thank you.
感覺他的詩越來越糟了
Think he's getting worse.
作為他的朋友  你應該告訴他實情
As his friend, you should probably tell him.
也許他的詩確實很棒
Maybe his poetry is great,
只是我們不懂得欣賞而已
we just don't know it yet.
咱們進這里玩吧
Let's go in here.
我想問問那個符號是什么意思
I want to ask what that symbol means.
克萊莉  我們進不去的
Clary, we'll never get in.
樂觀點好不好
Such the eternal optimist.
這太不像你了
This is so not like you.
就放縱一次嘛
Just go with it for once.
請問那個符號是什么意思
Hi. What does that symbol mean?
-什么符號  -對呀  哪有什么符號
- What symbol? - Yeah, what symbol?
-就在上面  你沒看見嗎  -沒有
- It's right there. You don't... You don't see it? - No.
厲害啊
Hey, that was cool.
我們很融入嘛
Yeah, we're fitting in.
跳吧  跟著感覺走
Move it, go with it.
克萊莉  你想要點喝的嗎
Clary, you want a drink?
好啊
Yeah.
克萊莉  克萊莉  你怎么了
Clary, Clary, what is it?
你沒看見嗎
You didn't see that?
我知道我看到了什么
I know what I saw.
他們殺了那個讓我們進去的男人
They killed the guy that let us in the club.
-你喝了什么嗎  -對  不  西蒙
- Did you drink something? - Yeah... No, Simon.
我聽說  有時候
You know, I've heard sometimes
他們會從通風口泵入迷幻劑之類的東西
they pump hallucinogenic stuff into the air vents
好讓人們玩得更盡興
to make sure people have a good time.
如果是那樣的話  你怎么沒事
Okay, then how come you're fine?
難道我們吸的不是同一種空氣
Did we breathe different air?
我不知道  還是快回家吧
I don't know. Let's just go home.
-你還好嗎  -我很好
- You okay? - Yeah, fine.
你睡了一整天
You've been sleeping all day.
而且你昨晚很晚才回來
And you didn't come home till late last night.
是  但我回來了  好嗎
Yeah, well, I'm home, okay?
你不能出去
Well, you can't go.
我又賣出了一幅畫
Well, I sold another painting.
我想和你一起慶祝
I wanted to celebrate with you.
慶祝什么  你就那么一個買家
To what, your one buyer?
那個家伙到底是誰
Who is this guy anyway?
他買你的畫  可能只是因為對你有意思
He probably just buys your stuff 'cause he's into you.
我敢肯定  你會像拴住盧克那樣拴著他
I'm sure you'll just string him along like you do with Luke.
你真的想跟我談這個
You really want to have that conversation?
什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
-西蒙  -他對我來說  就像哥哥一樣
- Simon. - He's like my brother.
我不覺得他是這么想的
I doubt he feels that way.
我要出去了
Okay, well, I'm gonna go.
不  不  你不能出去
No, no, you can't.
你真是無理取鬧
This is ridiculous.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
只是去爪哇瓊斯咖啡店而已
I'm just going to Java Jones.
-我的上帝  -別慌  是我
- Jesus! - No, just me.
走吧  西蒙
Come on, Simon.
克萊莉  我有事要告訴你  好嗎
Clary. There's something I want to tell you, okay?
我們可以晚點再談
We can talk about this later.
再見  費瑞太太
Bye, Mrs. Fray.
看  我突然畫了上百張這樣的符號
Look, suddenly I'm drawing hundreds of these things,
而我根本不知道這是什么
and I have no idea what they are.
我不明白  我看我是要瘋了
I don't know. I think I'm going out of my mind.
也許你就像《第三類接觸》里的主角一樣
You know, maybe you're like the guy in Close Encounters.
所有人都覺得他得了妄想癥
Everybody thought he was paranoid,
但結果發現是UFO
and then there turned out to be, well, UFO,
凡事都講得通的  比如...
reasonable, like...
上帝啊  這不是真的
Oh, God, this isn't happening.
-怎么了  -這不是真的
- What? - This isn't happening.
現在你真嚇到我了
Okay, now you're freaking me out.
克萊莉  你是不是...
Clary, are you...
你在看什么
what are you looking at?
在這等著
Wait here.
圣杯在哪里  喬瑟
Where's the Cup, Jocie?
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
那可多虧了你的女兒
You can thank your daughter for that.
為什么只有我能看見你
Why can I see you and no one else can?
我也想問你同樣的問題
I was going to ask you the same question.
我都不知道我為什么在跟你講話
I don't even know why I'm talking to you.
你是個殺人兇手  殘酷無情的殺手
You're a killer, a cold-blooded killer.
所以還有和平有愛的殺手嗎
As opposed to a peace-loving killer?
我知道我看到了什么
I know what I saw.
你覺得你知道
You think you know.
我為什么會畫這個
Why am I drawing this?
看來我是對的  你不是凡人
So I was right, you're not a mundane.
什么  凡人是什么意思
Excuse me? What's a mundane?
凡世間的普通人類
Someone from the human world.
如果我不是普通的人類  那我是什么
If I'm not a human, then what am I?
去找圣杯
Go find the Cup.
你這是從什么時候開始的
When did this start?
不  我為什么會畫這個
No, no. Why am I drawing this?
回答我
Answer me!
西蒙
Simon.
克萊莉母親來電
拒絕
也許你該接電話  可能是你男朋友
Maybe you should answer that. Could be your boyfriend.
-他不是我男朋友  -那他知道嗎
- He's not my boyfriend. - Does he know that?
拜托快接  很吵
Please. It's annoying.
媽媽  我馬上回來
Mom, I'm coming home.
不  不  不行  你不能回家
No, no, no. You can't come home.
明白嗎  你不要回家
You understand me? You don't come home.
打電話給盧克
You call Luke.
告訴他瓦倫萊還活著  他找到我了
Tell him Valentine's alive and that he found me.
我愛你
I love you.
-媽媽  -不  不要
- Mom! - No, no!
媽媽
Mom!
告訴瓦倫萊  他永遠不可能得到圣杯
You tell Valentine he'll never have the Cup.
別喝  過來  別  什么
Don't you... Don't drink... Come here! Don't... What?
快接電話
Come on.
對不起  對不起  你還好嗎
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You okay?
還好嗎  聽著  別動
All right, look, don't move, all right?
媽媽
Mom?
媽
好了  起來吧
Come on. Come on.
夠了  可以了  可以了
That's enough! That's enough. That's enough.
它已經死了
It's dead.
那玩意是什么
What the hell was that?
我說了  你也不會信的
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
說說看
Try me.
那是個惡魔
It was a demon.
你說得對
You're right.
我不相信
I don't believe you.
還有那個
And that thing,
你看見我在夜店里殺死的那個
that you saw me kill at the club, that...
也是惡魔
That was also a demon.
惡魔能寄主在任何生靈身上
Demons can take possession of any living creature.
任何人你都不能相信
You can't trust anyone.
甚至是你自以為了解的人
Even people you think you know.
那我為什么要相信你
So, why should I trust you?
我剛剛救了你的命啊
I did just save your life.
蘿西婭  開門  拜托
Dorothea, open up, please.
你能不能...
Can you...
你知道我媽媽到底出什么事了嗎
Do you know what happened to my mom?
你知道嗎
Do you?
等等  你看得見這家伙嗎
Wait, you can see this guy?
她當然可以  她是女巫
Of course she can. She's a witch.
怎么從姜餅屋搬到這么簡陋的一居室了
Downgraded from a gingerbread house to a one-bedroom?
你知道我媽媽去哪了嗎
Do you know where my mom is?
對不起  我不知道
Sorry. I have no idea.
她提到了一個人  叫瓦倫萊
Well, she mentioned a name... Valentine.
-你還是走吧  -不要  求你了
- You better leave. - No, please.
你必須告訴我  什么都行
Not until you tell me something, anything.
看看塔羅牌怎么說吧
Let's see what the cards have to say.
不好意思  但是我不相信這些
I'm sorry, but you know that I don't believe in any of...
坐下
Sit.
讓手在所有牌上掃過
Run your hands over the cards.
這套牌是我媽媽畫的
My mom painted these.
對  是送我的禮物
Yes. They were a gift.
看哪張牌會被選中
Let's see which card gets picked.
圣杯牌
The Ace of Cups.
-那是天使圣杯  -所以呢
- That's the Mortal Cup. - So?
別理他
Ignore him.
那是天使圣器
It's a Mortal Instrument,
我們族人的三大圣物之一
one of the three holy objects of my people.
這跟它有什么關系
What's it doing here?
這關我媽什么事
I don't understand what any of this has to do with my mom.
你媽媽曾是一名暗影獵人  和他一樣
Your mother was a Shadowhunter, like him.
不對  我媽媽是個畫家
No, my mom is a painter.
她從沒跟你提過這些  是不是
She never told you any of this, did she?
我只知道她失蹤了
All I know is that she's gone,
而我不知道要從何找起
and I have no idea where to start looking for her.
讓我來為你讀心
Let me read you.
有什么東西封住了你的記憶
There's something blocking your mind.
我猜是你媽媽為了保護你
My guess is your mother hired someone
找了法術高超的人幫忙
very skilled to protect you.
-保護我什么  -你自己的回憶
- From what? - Your own memories.
為什么
Why?
我有什么回憶她會希望我忘掉
I don't remember anything she'd want me to forget.
等等
Wait.
很高興認識你
Nice to meet you.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
你嚇到我了
You scared me.
這里發生了什么
What the hell happened here?
-我媽媽不見了  -什么
- My mom's missing. - What?
有人劫走了她  還把這里毀了
Someone took her and destroyed the place.
現在這個家伙在幫我找她
This guy is helping me find her,
但是你看不見他  而且他...
but you can't see him, and he...
克萊莉
Clary.
好極了
Great.
現在連我也看不見他了
Okay, now I can't see him, either.
我是杰斯·威蘭德  惡魔獵人
Jace Wayland, demon hunter.
我是西蒙·路易斯  鑰匙大師
Simon Lewis, Keymaster.
電影《捉鬼敢死隊》的角色  被惡魔附身
你是守衛者嗎
Are you the Gatekeeper?
我聽不懂你在說什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
什么情況  你現在能看見他嗎
Wait. What, so you can see him now?
-什么  我當然看得見  -我以為...
- What? Of course I can see him. - But I thought...
-不是  -你在說什么呢
- No... - What are you talking about?
太混亂了
This is so confusing.
這人是誰
Who's this?
是我爸爸  我兩歲的時候他就去世了
That's my dad. He died when I was two.
克萊莉  過來一下
Clary, a moment.
你媽媽剛剛失蹤
So, wait, your mom is gone,
你就跟這個染著黃發的哥特怪人混在了一起
and you're hanging around with some dyed-blond wannabe Goth weirdo?
你在哪里遇到的這個家伙
Where'd you come across this guy?
不是  是他來找的我
No, I didn't. He found me.
什么  他找的你
What? He found you?
-我知道這聽上去...-你得看看這個
- No, I know it sounds... - You should check this.
順便說明  我的金發是天生的
And for the record, my hair is naturally blond.
克萊莉  克萊莉  克萊莉  西蒙
Clary, Clary, Clary... Simon?
她給你打電話了嗎
She called you?
你怎么沒接
Why didn't you pick up?
如果知道事情這么嚴重  我肯定就接了
If I'd known it was serious, I would have picked up.
你不接  怎么知道嚴不嚴重
Well, how would you know if you didn't pick it up?
那是什么
What's that?
不是什么好東西
Nothing good.
你知道她從哪弄到的這東西嗎
Do you have any idea where she got this?
我得去找盧克
I've got to find Luke.
好奇怪  他的車在這
It's so weird. His truck's here.
來  這邊走
Come on. This way.
-你在這里等  -憑什么聽你指揮
- No, you wait here. - Who made you the boss?
沒關系  如果有人來了告訴我們一聲
It's okay. Just let us know if anyone comes.
我認識盧克這么多年
I've known Luke all these years,
但從沒有來過這下面
but I've never been down here.
什么
What?
說啊  伙計
Come on, mate!
聽好了
Now, listen...
我們只需要你實話實說  伙計
All you got to do, mate, is tell me the truth.
我告訴你了  我不知道圣杯在哪里
I'm telling you, I don't know where the Cup is.
我知道你和喬瑟關系親密
I know you and Jocie are close.
我可不傻  對吧
I'm not stupid, am I?
不用你回答我
Don't answer that.
仔細聽好了  只要說出天使圣杯在哪里
Listen to me, mate. Just tell me where the Mortal Cup is.
喬瑟就不會有事
And then Jocie will be fine.
-盧克  說吧  說實話  -我不知道
- Lukey, tell me. Tell me the truth. - I don't know.
別把我惹急了
You don't want to make me angry.
-我說過了  -是嗎
- I'm telling you... - Do you?
我再問一遍  圣杯在哪里
I'm going to ask you again, mate, where's the Cup, huh?
我不知道
I don't know.
我們要找的不是同一個東西嗎  小盧克
We all want the same thing, Lukey boy, don't we?
區別在于  我認為你知道東西在哪
Difference is, I think you know where it is.
對不對呀
Don't You?
快點  快點說呀
Come on. Come on. Talk!
我們得走了
We need to go.
不  拜托  你得幫幫他
No, please, you have to help him.
你不明白
You don't understand.
他們是瓦倫萊的手下
They work for Valentine.
他死定了  我幫不了他
He's a dead man. I can't help him.
他就像我的家人一樣
He's like family.
真是不可思議
You know what's really amazing
你看起來還真的很像人類
is how much you actually look like a human.
很不錯啊
Isn't it great?
求求你
Please.
你不生氣嗎  不變身嗎
Are you gonna get mad? You're going to change?
我想看你變身的樣子
I want to see you change.
快點讓我看看你怎么變身
Show me how you can change. Huh?
快看啊  快看啊
Look at that. Look at that.
狗娃就要現形了
Dog boy's coming on.
你想抱我的腿嗎
You want to hump my leg?
抱人的腿  你喜歡這個吧
You hump legs? You like that?
你想嗅我的屁股嗎
You want to smell my derriere?
趕快給我變身
I want to see you change!
你只需要說出喬瑟琳藏匿圣杯的地方
You just got to tell me where Jocelyn hid the Cup.
我們就把她還給你
Then you can have her back.
保證她安然無恙地回來
She'll be safe and sound.
我不想讓她回來
I don't want her back.
我一點都不在乎
I couldn't care less.
為了得到天使圣杯
I have spent years cozying up
我花了那么多年  親近她跟她的孩子
to that woman and her brat for the Mortal Cup.
潘伯恩  說真心話
Pangborn, listen to me.
我真希望親手把她交給瓦倫萊
I want to be the one to give her to Valentine.
是啊  沒錯
Yeah, right.
你犯了個大錯
You are making a big mistake.
我不相信你說的話  你相信他嗎
I don't believe you. Do you believe him?
-克萊莉  快逃  -克萊莉  聽我說
- Clary, run! - Clary, listen!
對不起  警官
Excuse me. Officer?
我想舉報一起入室搶劫事件
I'd like to report a break-in.
還有人口失蹤
And a missing person.
我朋友的家被人非法闖入
My friend's house got broken into, and...
-她媽媽不見了  -不  不
- Her mom's missing. - Oh, no.
快跑
Run!
-你居然殺了兩個警察  -他們不是警察
- You killed two cops! - They weren't cops.
快走
Let's go!
克萊莉
Clary.
你不能待在這里  他們會找到你的
You can't stay here. They'll find you.
盧克怎么能說他不在乎呢
How could Luke say that he didn't care?
我從記事起  就認識他了
I've known him for as long as I can remember.
過去他每天晚上都讀書給我聽
He used to read to me every night.
這么多年來  一直接我放學
He's been picking me up at school for years.
可能那些回憶都不是真的
Look, maybe those memories aren't real.
還記得我跟你說的嗎
Do you remember what I told you?
任何人你都不能相信
You can't trust anyone.
不行  我要找到我媽媽  我得回家
No, I need to find my mom. I have to go home.
我肯定漏掉了什么
There must be something that I missed!
聽我一句話
Listen to me, okay?
我們會想辦法解決的
We'll figure this out,
但不是在這里  也不是現在
but not here and not now.
我們得把你帶到安全的地方
We need to get you to a safe place.
我是暗影獵人  克萊莉
I'm a Shadowhunter, Clary,
我會用我的生命保護你
and I will protect you with my life.
你們在這呢  我以為你們就在后面
There you guys are. I thought you were right behind me.
還以為把你們弄丟了
I thought I'd lost you.
好吧  我跟你走
Okay. I'll follow you.
你確定嗎  他剛才殺了兩個警察
Are you sure about that? 'Cause he just killed two cops.
他們可不是警察
Yeah, they weren't cops.
我看他們就是警察
They looked like real cops to me.
他們不是真正的警察
They weren't real cops.
那他們哪來的警車
So, where did they get the car?
他們不是警察
They weren't real cops.
學院
到這里就安全了
We'll be safe in here.
這是什么破地方
What is this dump?
這可不是破地方
This isn't a dump.
只是你看不到而已
You just can't see it.
怎么回事  他們來這干什么
What the hell is going on? What are they doing in here?
-被惡魔咬傷了  -克萊莉
-It's a demon bite. - Clary.
杰斯  快想辦法
Jace, do something!
現在你是不是應該
Is this the part when you start
撕下衣服  給我包扎傷口
tearing off pieces of your shirt to bind my wounds?
你要是想讓我脫衣服
If you wanted me to take my clothes off,
直說就是了
you should've just asked.
發燒而已
It's just a fever.
她醒了
Hey. Hey, she's waking up.
我昏過去了  你們就給我弄了個紋身
I passed out, and you guys tattooed me?
我以為只有在拉斯維加斯才會發生這種事
Thought that only happened in Vegas.
-那不是紋身  -是咒符
- It's not a tattoo. -It's a rune.
他們什么樣的咒符都有
They have them for everything,
隱形  強化  治愈
they make you invisible, strong, they heal.
當然也有顯形的咒符
They also make you visible.
所以我才突然能看見他
That's why I could suddenly see him.
-就連餓的時候...  -不
- Even if you're hungry... - No.
咒符對你有效
The fact that the rune had an effect on you
正好解釋了你為什么能看見我們
explains why you can see us.
我不明白
I don't get it.
凡人無法承受咒符的力量
Mundanes can't survive the process.
咒符對他們來說太過強大  所以...
The runes are too strong for them, so...
現在我們百分百確定你有暗影獵人血統了
Now we definitely know you have Shadowhunter blood.
等等  之前不確定嗎
Wait, it wasn't definite before?
是的  她沒死  所以現在確定了
Well, it became definite when she didn't die. Yes.
給  看看合不合身
Here, see if these fit.
這里可不經常有客人來
It's not every day we get guests in here.
尤其是女生
Especially not girls.
對了
Oh, Yeah.
我們不該報警嗎
Shouldn't we call the cops?
我是說  那些真警察
I mean, the real ones.
真是個好主意
That's a great idea.
我們在過去的一千年里
I just don't know why we haven't thought of that
怎么就沒想到要這么做呢
for the past thousand years.
霍奇準備好見她了
Hodge is ready for her.
他想在圖書館單獨見她
He wants to see her alone in the library.
霍奇是誰
Who's Hodge?
整個學院由他負責
He's in charge of the Institute.
好吧  咱們走
Okay, let's go.
過去無數暗影獵人到這里尋求庇護
Hundreds of Shadowhunters used to seek asylum here.
但如你所見
But, as you can see,
現在只剩我們幾個了
right now, we're the only ones.
沒有了天使圣杯  我們正走向滅亡
Without the Mortal Cup, we're a dying breed.
如果你不是天生的暗影獵人
Either you're born of a Shadowhunter,
就得喝下圣杯里的血才能變為其中一員
or you have to drink from the Mortal Cup.
走不走
You coming?
感覺離布魯克林很遙遠吧
Pretty far from Brooklyn, isn't it?
離杰斯遠點
Stay away from Jace.
霍奇可能有些古怪
You may find Hodge a little eccentric,
但他是史上最偉大的暗影獵人之一
but he's one of the greatest Shadowhunters that's ever lived.
把這個給我
Here, give me that.
把一個陌生人帶到學院的中心之地
Don't you think it's a bit risky inviting
你不覺得有點冒險嗎
a complete stranger into the heart of the Institute?
不  我覺得我們能信任她
No. I think we can trust her.
她那個凡人朋友呢
And what about her mundane friend?
那是一時沖動
Well, that was impulsive.
你一沖動就容易出事
When you're impulsive, things go badly.
小心點
Just be careful,
治療心碎的咒符可是最痛苦的
the rune to fix a broken heart is the most painful one.
他們明天就會離開的  我保證
They'll be out of here in a day, I promise.
杰斯
Jace.
她曾是最杰出的暗影獵人之一
She was one of the best,
你母親
your mum.
可我不明白...
But I don't understand why...
昨天你還只是個普通的女孩
Yesterday you were just a normal girl.
今天你覺得  你的世界
Today you feel as though your whole world
發生了翻天覆地的變化
has been turned upside down.
你只需要知道一件事
There's only one thing you need to know.
你小時候聽到的故事
The stories you were told as a little girl
怪獸  噩夢
about monsters, nightmares,
篝火邊低語的傳說
legends whispered around campfires...
都是真的
They're all true.
-這是惡魔嗎  -沒錯
- Demon? - Yes.
這個也是惡魔嗎
Demon?
不  狼人不是惡魔
No. Werewolves aren't demons.
我們跟地下生物達成了和平公約
We have a truce with Downworlders.
地下生物
Downwolriders?
住在14街以南的人嗎
What is that, like people below 14th Street?
紐約市14街以南的區域稱為downtown
地下生物指代所有其他族群
Well, "Downworlders" pretty much sums everything up,
吸血鬼  狼人  術士
vampires, werewolves, Warlocks.
術士  酷
Warlocks. Cool.
要怎么才能殺死僵尸呢
So, how do you kill a zombie?
我們不殺僵尸
We don't.
當然了  他們本來就是死人
Of course, they're already dead.
不  他們根本不存在
No. They don't exist.
那就是大名鼎鼎的圣杯啊
So, that's the famous Cup everyone's talking about.
沒錯  不過那是復制品
A replica. But yes.
杰斯總是一副憤世嫉俗的樣子
You know, Jace has got a real chip on his shoulder.
如果你小時候  親眼見到自己父親被殺害
You would, too, if you saw your father murdered
你也會這樣的
when you were a child.
如果不是他  我們早就死了
If it weren't for him, we'd be dead.
雖然不想承認  但他多次救過我們的命
He saved our lives more times than I care to admit.
好吧
Right.
傳說
The legend goes,
十字軍戰士召喚了一位天使
the Crusaders summoned an angel,
天使拉杰爾
the Angel Raziel.
拉杰爾將其鮮血傾入杯中
Raziel poured his blood into a cup,
他們飲下杯中之血
and those who drank from it
成為一半人類一半天使
became half angel, half human.
就是暗影獵人
Shadowhunters.
他們的子孫后代沿承這個血脈
As did their children and their children's children.
我們擁有強大的力量
Beings of immense power,
足以維持世間平衡
strong enough to restore balance
保護世界  與邪惡為戰
and protect the world in a war against evil.
這是一場沒有勝利的戰爭
A war that can never be won,
但戰斗不能停止
but must always be fought.
惡魔不會輕易滅亡
Demons don't die easily.
而我們
Whereas we,
我們終有一死
we remained all too mortal.
為什么不用圣杯創造更多的暗影獵人呢
Why didn't they just use the Cup to create more Shadowhunters?
瓦倫萊也是這么說的
Valentine's exact words.
圣鑰會是圣杯的守護者
The Clave, the keepers of the Cup,
他們害怕使用圣杯的力量
they were afraid of using its power.
他們知道
They knew
喝了圣杯之血的人很少能夠活下來
that hardly anyone who drank from it survived.
瓦倫萊·摩根斯頓集結了一伙朋友
Valentine Morgenstern drew a circle of friends together,
一群年輕的充滿理想的暗影獵人
young, idealistic Shadowhunters,
幫助他從圣鑰會那里竊取了天使圣杯
to help him steal the Mortal Cup from the Clave.
然而他并不想保護人類
But he didn't want to protect humanity.
他堅信  暗影獵人必須要進化
He believed there had to be an evolution of Shadowhunters,
成為更加強大的種族
something more powerful.
于是  他開始用天使圣杯做實驗
He began experimenting, using the Mortal Cup.
他學會了召喚惡魔
He learned how to summon demons.
甚至給自己注射惡魔之血
He even injected himself with demon blood
來控制惡魔
so he could control them.
他想要統治一切
He wanted to rule.
你的母親為了阻止他
Your mother, to prevent that,
偷走了圣杯
stole the Cup from him,
消失得無影無蹤
and vanished into thin air.
可如果只有她知道圣杯在哪...
But if she's the only one that knows where the Cup is, then...
也許她不是唯一知情者
Maybe she isn't.
也許她告訴了別人
Maybe she told someone else.
只是當事人自己不知道而已
Someone who doesn't know she knows.
寂言兄弟準備好見她了
The Silent Brothers are ready for her.
霍奇怎么不一起來
Why didn't Hodge come with us?
他有很多年沒離開過學院了
He hasn't left the Institute in years.
聽說是因為一個咒語
Some say it's a spell.
他有曠野恐懼癥吧
He's agoraphobic.
就是他嗎
Is that him?
不  那是守墓人哈羅德
No, that's Harold, the groundskeeper.
那才是
That's him.
你確定要這么做嗎
Are you sure you want to go through with this?
我們會幫助你恢復記憶
We will help you to remember.
你會驚醒死靈的
You'll wake the dead.
真不敢相信  這地方就在城市邊上
I can't believe this place is just outside the city.
歡迎來到骸骨之城
Welcome to the City of Bones.
寂言兄弟就是在這里
This is where the Silent Brothers draw their power,
從暗影獵人的尸骨和骨灰中獲取力量
from the bones and ashes of Shadowhunters.
他們都葬在這里嗎
All of them are buried here?
是的
Yes.
未來某天  我會在這里
One day, that's gonna be me.
我只能送你到這了
This is as far as I go.
你會沒事的
You'll be fine.
你之前也這么做過嗎
So you've done this before?
沒有
No.
你要聽從自己的內心
You must listen with your mind.
媽媽
Mom?
出去  出去
Go. Go.
克萊莉  這是盧克
Clary, this is Luke,
我最好的朋友
my dearest friend.
你可以信任他
You can trust him.
你好  克萊莉
Hi, Clary.
不要跟別人說
Don't tell.
不要碰那件舊東西
Don't touch that old thing.
只是個舊杯子而已  克萊莉
It's just an old cup, Clary.
克萊莉  克萊莉  你沒事吧
Clary! Clary, are you okay?
克萊莉
Glary?
你思想的封印比我預計的還要強大
Your block is stronger than I anticipated.
只有施術者本人才能幫你解開
It can only be undone by the one who put it there.
我不知道施術的人是誰
I have no idea who put it there.
你寫下來了
You wrote it.
你的大腦記得倒像
Your mind remembers the inverted image.
只需要從另一個角度去看
Just have to look at it differently.
B A N E
"B-A-N-E."
-貝恩  -貝恩是誰
- Bane. - Who?
馬格納斯·貝恩  他是名術士
Magnus Bane. He's a warlock.
我早該猜到的
I should have known.
那我們去找他吧
Well, let's go talk to him then.
沒那么簡單
Not like that.
我們得需要伊莎貝爾的幫助
We're gonna need some help from Isabelle.
這就是件上衣
This is a top.
是裙子
It's a dress.
就是拉不下去
I can't pull this off.
你只要穿雙合適的鞋子...
Well, actually, with the right shoes...
不是...
No, I mean...
是這件裙子太緊了  緊緊貼在身上
This dress is so tight, it's like a second skin.
沒別的衣服可穿了嗎
Don't you have anything else?
如果讓人一眼就看出你是個凡人
If you go out looking like your mundane self,
我們是無法靠近馬格納斯·貝恩的
we won't get within a hundred feet of Magnus Bane.
他是布魯克林最高術士
He's the High Warlock of Brooklyn.
不要抱怨了  過來
Now, stop complaining, come over here.
拿著
Hold this.
那個叫埃利克的家伙不喜歡我
That guy Alec doesn't like me very much.
那個家伙是我哥哥
That guy Alec is my brother.
杰斯知道埃利克對他的感覺嗎
Does Jace know how Alec feels about him?
有那么明顯嗎
Is it that obvious?
其實沒什么大不了的
It's really not that big of a deal.
我也是這么想的
It isn't to me either.
但圣鑰會不這么想  規矩不是我定的
But it is to the Clave. I don't make the rules.
看到沒  你這樣挺漂亮的
See? You look pretty.
穿成跟妓女一樣  真能找到我媽媽嗎
How is being dressed like a hooker gonna help me find my mom?
說話注意點  那可是我的衣服
Easy now, those are my clothes.
她看上去很棒吧  埃利克
Doesn't she look great, Alec?
她看著就像那些
She looks like someone whose
把手機號碼貼在廁所墻上的人
phone number should be on a bathroom wall.
我覺得你看起來很棒
I think you look great.
不對  我來過這里
Wait, I've been here.
-等等  -怎么了
- Wait. - What?
那樣更好看嗎
Is that better?
是的
It's better.
哎呦呦
Well, well, well.
這是誰來了啊
Look-a here.
納非利  《圣經》中墜落天使與人類的后代
我怎么不記得邀請了納非利之裔
I don't remember inviting any children of the Nephilim.
馬格納斯·貝恩  我們得談談
Magnus Bane. We need to talk.
你知道我不喜歡你們族群
You know I don't like you guys.
但我不趕你們走  因為這位迷人的人士
But I'll let you stay, but only because of the hot one.
-謝謝  -謝謝
- Thanks. - Thank you.
什么
What?
我指的是他
I meant him.
藍眼睛那個
The one with the blue eyes.
還因為克萊莉
And because of Clary.
你怎么會認識她
Wait. How do you know her name?
跟我來
Come with me.
-你母親呢  -她失蹤了
- Where's your mother? - She's missing.
原來如此
That explains it.
她每年都會帶你過來
Every year, she brought you here.
從未失約過
She never missed an appointment.
我在你身上施的咒語是最完美的
Not every spell turns out as perfect as the one I did on you.
你只要一開始畫天使咒符
As soon as you started drawing the angelic rune,
就預示著你的記憶開始恢復
it was a sign your memory was surfacing.
這是我植入你腦海的
I had built that into your mind
這樣她才知道什么時候帶你過來
so that she knew when to bring you back.
你看到的關于暗影世界的一切
What you saw from the shadow world,
即使是親眼所見  你也會遺忘
you would forget, even as you saw it.
但隨著你年齡的增長
But as you grew older,
我需要愈加頻繁地為你施術
you needed my treatment more frequently.
她知道總有一天得告訴你真相
She knew she had to tell you one day,
但在你準備好之前
but until you were ready,
她想保持你記憶的封印
she wanted to keep the block on your mind.
這都是她要求的
It was exactly how she wanted it.
你覺得我們要在這里待多久
How long do you think we're gonna be here?
放松好嗎  西蒙
Relax, Simon, okay?
不要喝
Don't drink that!
西蒙  西蒙
Simon! Simon!
封印會隨時間逐漸消失
It'll wear off over time.
已經開始消失了  否則你也不會過來
It's already wearing off, or you wouldn't be here.
我需要記起來
I need to remember.
我媽媽情況危急
My mom doesn't have time.
求你了  你一定能幫我的
Please, there must be something you can do.
她的畫都是你買走的
You're the one who's been buying all my mom's paintings.
你為什么都買下來
Why did you buy all of them?
我知道她需要錢
I knew she needed the money.
我爸爸的肖像你都買了
You even have a portrait of my dad.
那不是你爸爸
That's not your dad.
他是一名在伊拉克陣亡的士兵
He's a soldier who died in Iraq.
喬瑟琳甚至都沒見過這個人
Jocelyn never even met the guy.
是有人請她畫這幅肖像的
She was asked to paint his portrait,
但是畫完后  士兵的遺孀太痛苦無法接受
but it was too painful for the widow.
你媽就把畫留下...
She kept the picture so...
假裝這是我爸爸
She could pretend he was my dad.
她做的一切都是為你好
Everything she did, she did for you.
你母親全部的人生
Your mother's whole existence,
逃跑  躲藏  謊言
the running, the hiding, the lies,
都是為了保護你
were to keep you safe.
她對我說的有一句是真話嗎
Was anything she ever told me true?
你的大腦中有一幅藏寶圖  克萊莉
There's a treasure map inside your head, Clary.
找到圣杯  它會指引你找到你的母親
Find the Cup, and it will lead you to your mother.
他們把西蒙帶走了
They've taken Simon.
-誰  -吸血鬼
- Who? - Vampires.
記住
Just remember,
你母親一直在躲避的是暗影獵人
it was Shadowhunters your mother was running from.
我們去找西蒙
Let's go find Simon.
我們不能私闖吸血鬼的巢穴
We can't break into a vampire's lair,
我們沒學過對付吸血鬼
we never learned.
-不要再說了  -杰斯  你知道規矩
- Don't start again. - Jace, you know the rules.
我們來這里干什么
Guys, what are we doing here?
不是要去找西蒙嗎
I thought we were trying to find Simon.
我們知道他在哪里
We know where he is.
但需要先拿點東西
We just need to pick up a few things.
這是什么  你們跟教堂之間的什么協議嗎
What is this, some kind of deal you have with the church?
惡魔隨時會以不同的形態
Demons exist all across the world
出現在世界各個角落
in their varying, different forms.
暗影獵人不信奉宗教
Shadowhunters cling to no particular religion,
但是所有宗教都會幫助我們
and in turn all religions assist us in our battle.
我們可以輕松進入猶太教會堂
We could have as easily gone to a Jewish synagogue
或是神社廟宇...
or a Shinto temple or...
找到了
Here it is.
每座教堂的圣壇下面
Beneath every altar in every church...
都會有這個
...you'll find this.
那你信仰什么
So, what do you believe in?
我信我自己
I believe in myself.
我知道我的職責是斬殺惡魔
I know my job is to kill demons.
所以我不用信仰別的
I don't have to believe in anything else.
那天使拉杰爾呢
What about the Angel Raziel?
那個故事很動聽
Yeah, makes for a nice story.
-但霍奇認為...-霍奇啊
- But Hodge thinks... - Yeah, Hodge.
他得多出來走走
He needs to get out more.
-我覺得...-聽著
- I thought... - Listen,
我三分之一的人生都在獵殺惡魔
I've been hunting demons for over a third of my life,
但是我從未見過天使
and in all that time, I've never seen an angel.
給你
Here.
給你  你拿這個
Here, you take this one.
我不會...
I don't...
我教你
Here, let me show you.
這是專殺吸血鬼的槍  必須刺穿心臟
It's a vampire gun. Must pierce the heart.
抵在對方的胸口
Push it up against the chest.
開槍
Fire.
上膛  然后就可以再用了
Recharge. Then you're good to go again.
死亡旅館
Hotel of Death?
他們還是很有幽默感的
You can't say they don't have a sense of humor.
走吧
Come on.
-你跟她是怎么回事  -她很勇敢
- What is it about her? - She's brave.
我們是暗影獵人  我們都很勇敢
We're Shadowhunters, we're all brave.
她以前不知道  她跟我們不同
She wasn't raised like us, she's different.
她會把我們都害死的
She's gonna get us all killed.
這是西蒙的襯衣
Simon's shirt.
他在這里
He's up here.
西蒙
Simon.
-天哪  天哪  西蒙  -克萊莉
- Oh, my God, oh, my God, Simon. - Clary.
別拉我  我快夠到他了
No, I can feel him!
幫我一把  加油
Give me a hand. Come on, come on.
爛靴子
These damn boots!
來
Here.
接住
Here you go.
-好了  -慢慢來
- Come on. - Guys, steady.
慢慢來
Slowly.
他還活著
He's alive!
小心
Careful.
快走  他們要的不是我
Go on. Get out. They don't want me.
他們要的是你  他們想要圣杯
They want you, they want the Cup.
-快  走吧  -天哪
- Come on. Let's go. - Oh, God.
快走
Let's go!
這邊
No, here.
-這邊  -快走
- In here! - Go!
杰斯
Jace.
你后面
Behind you!
快走  快走
Come on! Come on!
克萊莉
Clary!
他們人數太多了
There's too many of them.
有點信心  行嗎
Have a little faith.
快走
Run!
杰斯  給我匕首
Jace, I need a knife.
-太陽出來了  -快走吧
- The sun. - Let's go.
你去幫西蒙
You help Simon.
克萊莉
Clary!
堅持住
Hold on!
克萊莉
Clary!
謝謝
Thank you.
謝謝你救了西蒙
For saving Simon.
-你還好嗎  -沒事  我沒事
- Are you okay? - I'm okay, I'm okay.
克萊莉
Clary.
我能跟你聊聊嗎
Can I talk to you?
好  我正打算去看西蒙
Yeah, I was just gonna go see Simon.
-我希望你離開這里  -什么
- I want you to leave here. - What?
你差點害死我們
You almost got us killed.
很抱歉  但我們別無選擇
I'm sorry, we didn't have a choice.
難道能對西蒙見死不救嗎  而且杰斯...
I mean, we had to save Simon, and Jace...
杰斯是那種想要拯救世界的人
Jace thinks he needs to save the world.
不過不需要你來鼓勵他
But you don't need to encourage him to do it.
-這不是你們的責任嗎  -沒錯
- But that's what you guys do. - Yes, us.
這是我們的責任
What we do.
我們是個隊伍  而你只是累贅
We're a team, you're deadweight.
-一個凡人  -我不是凡人
- A mundane. - I'm not a mundane.
如果你真如自己聲稱的那樣勇敢
And if you were half as brave as you pretend to be,
你就該承認..
you'd admit that...
什么
What?
你就該承認你愛杰斯
You'd admit that you're in love with Jace,
所以你才這么希望我離開
and that's what this is really about.
你敢再說這樣的話
If you ever say anything like that again...
我就殺了你
I'll kill you.
-我昏迷了多久  -一整天
- How long was I out? - All day.
我找到了你的眼鏡
Found your glasses.
-一個鏡片破了  -好吧
- One of the lenses cracked. - Yeah.
真奇怪
How weird.
我似乎不需要眼鏡了
I don't seem to need them anymore.
你在畫什么
So, what are you drawing?
沒什么
Nothing.
-好多了嗎  -對
- You okay? - Yeah.
真是太瘋狂了
It was crazy.
很抱歉我一開始不相信你
I'm sorry I didn't believe you before.
現在我相信了
Now I get it.
而且
And...
我一定是昏迷了
And I must have passed out,
然后你出現了
and then you showed up.
聽我說
Listen,
我知道一直以來  都是我比較需要你
I know I've always been the one who needed you
而你不需要我
more than you needed me.
-別瞎想  -是真的
- That's not true. - Yes, it is,
但我不在乎
but I never cared.
一直以來我只有媽媽  盧克  還有你
I've only ever had my mom, Luke and you.
所以別覺得你對我來說不重要
Don't ever imagine that you weren't important to me.
-好  -那就好
- Okay. - Okay.
知道了
Yeah.
那架鋼琴怎么惹你了
What did that piano ever do to you?
你彈得就好像失去了至愛一樣
You play it like you've lost your only love.
很不幸  我唯一的真愛只有我自己
Unfortunately, my one true love remains myself.
是嗎  那你至少不用擔心被拒絕
Well, at least you don't have to worry about rejection.
倒也不一定
Not necessarily.
有時候我會拒絕自己  這樣才不會很悶
I turn myself down occasionally just to keep it interesting.
你的琴聲的確飽含情感
You do play that with a lot of passion.
這正是問題所在  我彈得太有感情了
Well, that's the problem. I play it with too much emotion.
彈鋼琴本應只是單純音律的顯現
It's supposed to be played with a simple representation
不該有情感的展現
of notes, no interpretation.
音樂就應該賦予情感
Music is supposed to have emotion.
惡魔對兩個交錯的音調很敏感
Demons react to certain frequencies when two tones cross.
這會令他們發狂
Drives them crazy.
巴赫發現了這一點  然后寫下了樂譜
See, Bach discovered this and put it into a system using
結合音調連續的變換
a mathematical progression of tonal combinations
讓惡魔現身
that allows us to expose demons.
所以巴赫也是暗影獵人嗎
So Bach was a Shadowhunter?
-對  -所以
- Yes. - So...
所以巴赫的音樂對惡魔的影響
Bach is to demons what
就像大蒜對吸血鬼的效果
garlic is to vampires.
算是吧
Kind of.
不過  大蒜會用完
I mean, you can run out of garlic.
而音樂取之不盡
You can't really run out of music.
那是你放玩具的地方嗎
Is that where you keep all your toys?
比玩具好玩多了
It's way more fun.
過來
Come on.
這是傳送門
It's a portal.
就像百慕大三角一樣  是自然形成的
Like the Bermuda Triangle, it's a natural phenomenon.
學院就圍它而建
The Institute was built around it.
有些人說學院是紐約的第一棟建筑
Some say that the Institute was the first building in New York.
所以...
So it's...
構成空間的元素不僅僅是直線
Dimensions aren't all just straight lines.
還有曲線
There's bends,
折線和折角
folds and nooks.
解釋起來有些復雜  不過
It's a little bit difficult to explain, but
傳送門可以帶你去
the Portal can take you
這個維度空間里的任何地方
wherever you want to go in this dimension.
當你穿過這層表面
So, as soon as you break that surface,
就會被送到你內心深處最渴望的地方
you're transported to wherever your deepest thoughts lie.
所以就是
So that means...
-我媽媽那里...-等等
- My mom... - Wait.
我們從出生起  一直在學習如何使用它
We spend our entire lives training how to use it,
練習在踏入之前  想象自己要去的地方
visualizing where it will take us before we step into it,
這需要很強的注意力
and that takes incredible focus.
如果你沒接受訓練  就直接進去
If you were to step into it without the proper training,
你可能會跌入邊緣之境
you could end up in limbo,
永遠迷失在自己的思想里
lost in your own mind forever.
過來
Here.
我給你展示一下
Let me show you.
來吧
Come on.
不許偷看
No peeking.
很帥吧
Pretty cool, isn't it?
好了
Now...
我們
You and I...
還要慶祝生日呢
Have a birthday to celebrate.
你怎么知道的
How did you know?
為找到你  我做了調查
Research. When I was trying to find you.
現在沒人會來這里了
No one comes up here anymore.
這個地方完全屬于我們
We have the place to ourselves.
這里好美
This is breathtaking.
抱歉我沒有準備蛋糕
Sorry there's no cake.
我根本沒想到會有慶祝
Well, I was expecting nothing,
所以已經很棒了
so this is great.
每個人的生日都應該收到禮物
Well, everyone should get something for their birthday.
你收到過什么禮物
What did you get?
大多數是武器
Weapons mostly.
你肯定不覺得驚訝
I'm sure that doesn't surprise you.
現在的我很難驚訝了
At this point, nothing really does.
我九歲的時候
When I was nine...
我爸爸送了我一只獵鷹
my father gave me a falcon.
他說讓我馴服它
He told me to make it obedient.
要我把它弄瞎
I was supposed to keep the bird blind,
但是我下不了手
but I couldn't bring myself to do it.
我輕撫它的翅膀  直至得到它的信任
Instead, I touched and stroked its wings until it trusted me.
我把它馴服得乖順至極
I tamed it to perfection.
帶去給我爸爸看
I took it to my father,
還以為他會為我自豪
expecting him to be proud of what I'd done.
他說
He said,
"我讓你馴服它"
"I told you to make it obedient.
"而你卻讓它愛你"
"Instead, you taught it to love you.
"你沒有馴服它  你毀了它"
"You didn't tame it, you broke it."
然后他搶走了獵鷹  折斷了它的脖子
Then he took the bird and he broke its neck.
我哭了整晚  之后再也沒有哭過
I cried all night and I never cried again.
你最終原諒他了嗎
Did you ever forgive him?
他是為了讓我更強大
He did it to make me stronger.
這是代表威蘭德嗎
Does that stand for Wayland?
到午夜了
Midnight.
看好
Watch this.
When your soul finds the soul it was waiting for
When someone walks into your heart
Through a open door
When your hand finds the hand
一般女孩說想要塊大石頭
When a girl says she wants a big rock,
It was meant to hold
并不是真的指石頭
she doesn't literally mean a big rock
每位暗影獵人都應該擁有自己的巫光石
Every Shadowhunter should have their own witchlight.
Don't let go
When you're one with the one you were meant to find
我們有作伴的了
We have company.
Opened up to the light
那是霍奇的鳥
That's Hodge's bird.
That was kept inside your soul
我們該走了
We should probably go.
Don't let go
Someone comes into your life
It's like they've been in your life forever
No there's no one else's eyes
That could see into me
No one else's arms can lift
Lift me up so high
Your love lifts me out of time
And you know my heart by heart
我們真的該走了
We should definitely go.
And you know my heart by heart
剛才那個噴水系統  抱歉
Sorry about the sprinkler system.
我忘了還有那回事了
I forgot about that.
你要睡覺了嗎
You going to sleep?
你不累嗎
Well, aren't you tired?
我從未這樣清醒過
I've never been more awake.
-西蒙  我還以為你...-睡了嗎
- Simon, I thought you were... - Asleep?
我剛才是在睡覺
Yeah, I was.
我們只是...
We were just...
下一次如果你先說清楚
Next time, it might be a nice idea
你床上還有別的男人的話
to mention that you already have a man in your bed,
我們也許就不會這么尷尬了
so we can avoid such uncomfortable situations.
你邀請他上床了嗎
You invited him to bed?
很可笑  是吧
I know, it's ridiculous, isn't it?
這么多人怎么擠得下一張床
We would never have all fit.
我沒邀請他上我的床
I didn't invite him into bed.
我們只是在接吻而已
We were just kissing.
你這么快就否決了我們的愛
How swiftly you dismiss our love.
杰斯
Jace?
西蒙  已經很晚了  抱歉打擾到你了
Simon, it's late, and I'm sorry we woke you.
我也是
So am I.
去啊  去追他  去給他道歉
Go ahead. Go after him, go apologize to him,
去告訴他  他在你心中有多特別
go tell him just how special he really is.
-別總是這樣  -哪樣
- Stop acting like that! - Like what?
好像沒什么能傷害你一樣
Like nothing ever hurts you.
也許你在吻我之前
Well, maybe you should have thought about that
就該想到這點
before you kissed me.
我吻你
I kissed you?
算了  這對我來說也不是那么特別
Don't worry, it wasn't that special for me either.
真的很抱歉  西蒙  但你剛才...
I'm really sorry, Simon, but weren't you just in the...
我只是在找你
I was just looking for you.
-你要去哪兒  -回家
- Where are you going? - Home.
很顯然我在這里呆得太久了
It's clear I overstayed my welcome.
我道歉   一切發生的太突然了
Look, I'm sorry, okay? It wasn't like it was planned.
讓我猜猜  你們是情之所至  拜托
Let me guess, it just happened. Please.
我知道你不喜歡他  但是...
Look, I know you don't like him, but...
事實上  我討厭他
Actually, I hate the guy.
為什么
Why?
我覺得你該找個更好的人
I thought you were better than that.
你這是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
我才是那個一直伴你左右的人  不是他
I'm the one who's always been there for you, not him.
我一直愛著你
I'm in love with you.
顯然你對我沒感覺
And it's clear that you don't feel the same way.
-這...-別說了
-It's... - Don't.
沒什么好說的
There's nothing to say.
克萊莉
And, Clary,
他只是在利用你找圣杯
he's just using you to get the Cup.
西蒙
Simon...
強化咒符
靜聲咒符
除了你  只有你的母親可以做到這個
Your mother was the only other person who could do that.
但我之前從未能這樣做過
But I've never been able to do this before.
顯然封印不止封塵了你的記憶
Apparently the block wasn't just repressing your memories,
也壓制了你的能力
but your abilities as well.
-杰斯  我...-別說  讓我猜猜
- Jace, I... - Don't tell me.
你突然想畫畫  所以要找個人體模特
You have a drawing emergency and you need a nude model.
-我沒有興致  -聽我說
- I'm not in the mood. - Listen!
我知道我媽媽把圣杯藏在哪兒了
I know where my mom hid the Cup.
你好呀
Hey.
-你好  -克萊莉...
- Hi. - Clary...
你看起來很不一樣
Wow, you look different.
這都是我借來的
Yeah, it's just something I borrowed.
這身裝扮很棒  很漂亮
I mean, nice outfit. It's good.
我現在不方便說話  抱歉
Yeah, I can't talk now. Sorry.
西蒙  我剛在克萊莉家附近碰到了她
-克萊莉  -我是為塔羅牌來的
- Clary. - I came for the tarot cards.
-為什么  -我需要它
- Why? - I need them.
就是我媽媽畫的那一副
You know, the ones that Mom painted?
給我看一眼就行
I just need to look at them really quickly,
然后就還給你  我保證
and I'll give them back, I promise.
那些武器可不能帶進來
Those can't come in here.
這里是和平之家
This is a peaceful house.
把它們放在那兒
Put them in there.
你今天過得如何
How are you feeling today?
不錯  還可以
Fine. Just fine.
年輕人  那架鋼琴音不準了
Young man, that piano is out of tune.
別彈了
Please don't.
年輕人
Young man.
別彈了
Stop!
這支曲子
That song.
我不喜歡
Not one of my favorites.
住手
Stop!
給我看看
Let's have a look.
快出去
Get out!
蘿西婭夫人  你看到克萊莉了嗎
Hey, Madame Dorothea. Have you seen Clary?
我剛收到短信說她在這里
I just got a text that said she was here.
沒有
No.
好吧  我只是...
Okay. Well, I'll just...
西蒙
Simon!
西蒙  這不是她本人
Simon, it's not really her!
西蒙
Simon!
我來看著他
I'll take care of him.
西蒙
Simon!
圣杯在她手上
She's got the Cup!
西蒙
Simon!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
杰斯
Jace!
咒符沒有用
The runes aren't working.
西蒙  你過來
Simon, you follow me.
把這些剪開
You cut these up.
走開  你做的已經夠多了
Don't. You've done enough.
別那樣和她說話  那不是她的錯
Don't talk to her like that. This isn't her fault.
你說得對  這都是你的錯
No, you're right. This is your fault.
伊莎貝爾
Isabelle!
埃利克一直跟你說  你會受傷的
Alec kept telling you that you were going to get hurt.
你會讓我們都受傷的
You were going to get us all hurt.
現在要死的卻是他
Now he's the one dying.
我們必須找到天使圣杯
Well, we needed to get the Mortal Cup.
但不是通過害死你最好的朋友
But there were other ways to do it than
來找到它
getting your best friend killed.
你去把霍奇找來吧
Why don't you go get Hodge.
我從來沒想過讓埃利克出事
I never wanted anything to happen to Alec.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我們發誓共進退  我們是一個團隊
We agreed to do this together. We're a team.
克萊莉來了后  我們就不是一個團隊了
Since Clary got here, we haven't been a team.
霍奇
Hodge!
埃利克的傷勢惡化了
Alec's getting worse.
我知道
I know.
我已經去請人幫忙了
I've already sent for someone.
你拿到圣杯了嗎
Did you get the Cup?
接下來怎么辦
What now?
霍奇
Hodge?
你根本不清楚
You have no idea what it's like
背負著圣鑰會的詛咒是怎樣的
living with the Clave's curse,
無法踏足外面的世界
unable to set so much as a foot outside,
甚至連開扇窗戶都不敢
afraid to even open a window.
不要苛責我  克萊莉
Try not to judge me too harshly, Clary.
霍奇  你做了什么
Hodge, what have you done?
我就知道你能把圣杯帶給我
I always knew you would bring me the Cup.
只不過是早晚的問題
It was only a matter of time.
她在哪兒
Where is she?
她很好
She's fine.
你得到你想要的了  放了她
You got what you want. Now let her go.
我得確保你給我的是真的才行
I have to make sure you gave me the real one.
所有人都出于錯誤的動機爭奪升杯
Everybody wants the Cup for the wrong reason.
你就沒有錯嗎
And you don't?
有了圣杯
With this Cup,
我可以凈化我們的血脈
I can cleanse our bloodlines,
拯救我們的族群
save our race.
你可能不太了解凡人的歷史
You might not know much about mundane history,
但我可以告訴你
but I can tell you
當人們想要保護一個種族的時候
when people start talking about preserving a race,
結果往往不盡人意
it never goes well.
所以我媽媽傾盡人生將它藏起來
That's why my mom spent her whole life hiding it from you.
不
No.
她藏的不是圣杯
She wasn't hiding the Cup.
而是你
She was hiding you.
喝了它
Drink.
我不會喝的
I'm not gonna drink that.
你怕什么
Why are you so afraid?
你還沒出生的時候就喝過
You've been drinking this since before you were born.
你還在你媽肚子里時  我就給她喝過
I fed it to your mother while you were in her womb.
得了吧  克萊莉
Come on, Clary.
你肯定已經猜出來了
You must have guessed by now.
你母親一直極力掩蓋的
All these amazing talents
你的這些驚人天賦
that your mother so desperately tried to suppress,
你以為它們都是從哪兒來的
where do you think they came from?
你是我女兒
You're my daughter.
你血管里流的是我的血
My blood runs in your veins.
現在...
Now...
喝了它
Drink.
Drink!
把它拿出來
Take that out!
不
No!
有人剛剛通過了傳送門
Someone just went through the Portal.
我去看看
I'll go check.
抱歉
Sorry.
有點太激動了
I got a bit carried away.
盧克  你是一個...
Luke, you're a...
克萊莉  聽我說  聽我說  別害怕
Clary, listen to me, listen. Don't be afraid.
-聽我說  -別碰我
- Listen, right? - Don't touch me!
沒必要這樣
Hey, there's no need for that.
那東西會回來的
That thing will be back.
我們在外面不安全
We are not safe out here.
為了躲避瓦倫萊  我跳進了傳送門里
I jumped through the Portal to get away from Valentine.
我以為會去到我媽媽那里
I thought I'd end up with my mom.
結果我卻來到了最不想去的地方
Instead, I ended up in the last place I wanted to be.
聽著  傳送門把你送到這兒
Listen, the Portal brought you here
是因為你當時肯定在想著我
because you must have been thinking of me.
在你內心深處  你知道你可以信任我
Deep inside, you know you can trust me.
你說你完全不在乎我倆會發生什么
You said you couldn't care less what happened to either of us.
你只是想要圣杯  就跟所有人一樣
You just want the Cup, like everyone else.
我那么說是為了保護你  我還能怎么做
I said that to protect you. What else could I do?
這段時間我一直在關注著你
Been keeping an eye on you this whole time.
在旅館那里的是你
That was you at the hotel.
順便說一句  扔得漂亮
Good throw, by the way.
我怎么辦
What about me?
你怎么了
What about you?
我們有約在先
We had a deal.
我依舊沒拿到圣杯  不是嗎
Well, I still don't have my Cup, do I?
我遵守了我的承諾
I held up my end of the bargain.
不  你沒有
No, you didn't.
我把圣杯給了你
I gave you the Cup.
是你把它給了克萊莉  那不是我的錯
You handed it to Clary. That's not my fault.
解除我的詛咒
Now lift it.
聽著  那都是你腦中的幻象
Listen, it's all in your head.
不  不是
No. No!
有一個咒語
There's a spell.
是嗎  咒語
Really? A spell?
那只是你逃避真正問題的借口
That's just an excuse for a real problem
這里的問題
in there.
你真以為我能治好你
Do you really think I can fix that?
我給你圣杯  你驅走我的恐懼
I give you the Cup, you take away the fear.
沒有圣杯  我跟你一樣被困住了
Without the Cup, I'm as stuck as you are.
只是我的恐懼是真實的
Except my fear is real.
每個地下生物
Every Downworlder,
圣鑰會的每一位成員
every member of the Clave,
傳送門兩邊的每一個暗影獵人
every Shadowhunter on both sides of the Portal
現在都在找我
is looking for me right now.
我要盡可能取得所有的幫助
I'm going to need all the help I can get.
你沒必要這么做  瓦倫萊
You don't have to go through with this, Valentine.
還從來沒有惡魔涉足過學院
A demon has never set foot in the Institute.
也許現在是時候涉足了
Well, maybe it's time they did.
這一刻我等了這么多年
I've been waiting all these years to do this.
克萊莉讓我別無選擇
Clary's given me no choice.
她會回來的
She'll come back.
是嗎
Really?
你怎么能這么確定
And what makes you so sure?
這里有一個她在乎的人
There's someone here
她對他的感情跟對她母親的一樣深
she wants as much as her mother.
如果你騙他們說  他倆都是你的孩子
If you lie and tell them they're both your children,
就會傷透他們的心
you'll break their hearts.
我還能說什么呢
What can I say?
心碎之人是最好的追隨者
The broken make the best followers.
看看你
Look at you.
愛就是毀滅
To love is to destroy.
霍奇到底在哪兒
Where the hell is Hodge?
時間不多了
We don't have much time.
-你看這樣對嗎  -不對
- Does this look right to you? - No.
看
Hey, look.
馬格納斯
Magnus?
這些全部都需要  需要很多
I'm going to need all of this. Lots of it.
拿著這個
Take this.
封鎖這個地方
Lock this place down.
非盟友者  誅盡殺絕
Those who are not allies must be killed.
別動
Don't do that!
瓦倫萊
Valentine.
喬納森
Jonathan.
你怎么知道我的真名
How do you know my real name?
沒有人那么叫我
Nobody calls me that.
是真的嗎
Is it true?
瓦倫萊是我父親
Is Valentine my father?
他曾經是個很偉大的人
You know, he was a great man,
但他和圣鑰會發生了沖突
until his conflict with the Clave.
你媽媽帶著圣杯逃走之后
But when your mother ran away with the Cup,
他非常害怕圣鑰會報復他
he was just so afraid of retribution from the Clave,
所以他把自己的家燒為灰燼
he burned their house down to the ground.
他想讓別人都認為他已經死了
He wanted the world to believe he was dead.
在灰燼里  我們找到了一個男人
In the ashes, we found the remains of a man
和一個孩子的殘骸
and a child.
等等  還有個孩子
Wait a second, there was a child?
瓦倫萊惱羞成怒  他想讓她相信
Valentine was so enraged, he wanted her to believe
他殺死了自己以及他們的兒子
he killed himself and their son,
你的哥哥
your brother.
我有一個哥哥
I have a brother?
喬納森·克里斯托弗·摩根斯頓
Jonathan Christopher Morgenstern.
你撒謊
You're lying.
我的名字是杰斯·威蘭德
My name is Jace Wayland.
我是威蘭德家的人
And my family are the Waylands.
你以為克萊莉是唯一被封印記憶的人嗎
You think Clary is the only one with a block in her mind?
讓我把真相展示給你
Let me show you the truth.
你沒有馴化它  你毀了它
You didn't tame him. You broke him.
不  你...
No! You...
你不是我父親
You are not my father.
我回來幫你找回真正的自己
I came back to help you understand who you really are.
我知道你在這里不開心
I know you're unhappy here.
被規矩所束縛
Plagued by rules.
你的位置
Your place
在我旁邊
is next to me.
你是摩根斯頓家的人
You're a Morgenstern.
你是我的兒子
And you're my son.
我的名字是杰斯·威蘭德
My name is Jace Wayland.
我是威蘭德家的人
I'm a Wayland.
抱歉告訴你這個
Sorry to break this to you,
但到你了解真相的時候了
but it's time you heard the truth.
不要
Don't.
只需要換一個角度看
It's all a matter of perception.
你看  摩根斯頓
You see, Morgenstern.
-拿著這個  -好的
- Take this. - Okay.
好的
Okay.
伊莎貝爾
Isabelle.
克萊莉
Clary?
我們找到你母親了
Yeah, we found your mom.
他們找到她了
They found her.
她在學院里
She's at the Institute.
阿拉里克
Alaric.
我是盧克  你看到了嗎
It's Luke. Can you see it?
是的  我看到了
Yeah, I see it.
伙計們  我們得走了
Hey, guys, we have to go.
盧克需要我們
Luke needs us.
我們要去哪兒
Where are we headed?
去學院
The Institute.
我們會違反和平公約的
We'd be breaking the Accords.
我們保持人形就不會了
Not if we stay human.
走了  伙計們
Let's go, guys!
走  走  走
Go, go, go, go!
快點  出發
Come on, move it!
準備好了
Ready to go!
我都跟他們說了
They've all been briefed.
這是阿拉里克  是我們中的一員
This is Alaric. He's one of us.
請隨意
Go ahead.
如果需要的話  你可以把頭伸出窗外
You can hang your head out the window if you need to.
我是個狼人
I'm a werewolf
不是金毛獵犬
not a golden retriever.
西蒙
Simon!
在這兒等著  我馬上回來
Just wait here, I'll be back.
什么  不  伊莎貝爾  我不能...
What? No. Isabelle, I can'tjust...
不  伊莎貝爾
No. Isabelle!
快回來  伊莎貝爾  你在哪兒
Come on, Isabelle, where are you?
好了  行動
All right, move it!
快點  行動
Come on, move it!
好吧
All right.
狼人來救我們了
The werewolves are here to save us.
從沒想過我會這么說
Never thought I'd say that.
終于來了  伊莎貝爾
Finally! Isabelle.
打開門
Hey, open up the door.
他有反應了
It looks like he's responding.
他會活下來的
He'll survive.
小心
And be careful.
你們被入侵了
You're being invaded.
召喚那些該死的惡魔...
Summoning all these bloody demons...
跑
Run!
快跑
-我們去哪兒  -還有一個出口
- Where are we going? - There's another exit!
等等
Wait.
伊莎貝爾
Isabelle!
-我差點殺了你  -是的
- I almost killed you. - Yeah.
你還好嗎
Hey. You okay?
-是的  我沒事  -走吧
- Yeah, yeah. I'm fine. - Come on.
這地方到處都是惡魔
This place is full of demons.
這不可能
That's impossible.
學院是圣地
The Institute is hallowed ground.
好像沒人告訴過他們
Yeah, no one seems to have told them that.
肯定是里面的人放他們進來的
Someone on the inside must have let them in.
這是營救行動
This is a rescue mission.
我們對付不了惡魔
We are not equipped to fight demons.
-快散開  -往那邊走
- Spread out! - That way! That way!
退回去  快點
Move back! Come on!
我們這兒需要人手  阿拉里克
We could use some help here, Alaric!
阿拉里克
Alaric!
這兒肯定有別的出口吧
Come on, there must be some other way out of here, right?
沒有  西蒙
No, there isn't, Simon!
我們快頂不住了
We can't hold them much longer!
讓開
Step away.
快讓開
Step away!
克萊莉  這是哪個咒符
Clary, which rune is that?
我也不知道  這個是...
I don't know, it's just...
-這咒符我從來沒見過  -真的嗎
- I've never seen it before. - Really?
書里沒有
It's not in the book.
咒符要消失了
It's fading.
拿著  他們肯定是從哪里進來的
Here, they're coming in through somewhere.
我得去攔住他們
I'm going to stop them.
走吧
Come on.
你們先走
You guys go.
我們斷后
We'll catch up.
不要
No!
他們是從屋頂進來的  這邊來
They're coming from the dome. Come on.
喬瑟琳
Jocelyn,
你一直在我的心中
you never left my heart.
讓我帶你回家吧
I've come to take you home.
她哪也不去
She's not going anywhere.
你是怎么到這兒的
How did you get up here?
你擁有的能力超乎我的期望
You're even more powerful than I anticipated.
離她遠點
Get away from her.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
先聽聽他說的吧
Just listen to what he has to say.
事情跟你想的不一樣
It's not what you think.
終于
Finally...
我的兩個孩子團聚了
Both my children together.
我的女兒
My daughter
和我的兒子
and my son.
對不起  克萊莉
I'm so sorry, Clary.
我之前不知道
I didn't know.
瓦倫萊在說謊
Valentine's lying.
你父親是邁克爾·威蘭德
You're Michael Wayland's son.
盧克說我哥哥在火災中被燒死了
Luke said my brother is dead. He died in a fire,
他們在廢墟中發現了他的遺骸
and they found his remains in the ashes.
我逃走的時候  帶走了喬納森
I took Jonathan with me when I ran.
那副骸骨是一個被狼人殺死的孩子
The bones were of a child killed by wolves.
我也希望這不是真的
I wish it wasn't true.
她不愿相信你
She doesn't want to believe you
因為她愛著你  喬納森
because she is in love with you, Jonathan.
我還以為你叫杰斯
I thought your name was Jace.
杰斯是個昵稱
Jace is a nickname.
喬納森·克里斯托弗
Jonathan Christopher...
J.C.
杰斯
Jace.
那有個控制桿
There's the lever.
你去把屋頂關上  我來驅趕它們
You go close the dome and I'll hold them off.
把圣杯拿出來  克萊莉
Take out the Cup, Clary.
把我的圣杯拿出來
Take out my Cup!
我要那個圣杯
I want that Cup!
你說過  你不會傷害她
You said you wouldn't hurt her!
夠了
Enough!
適可而止
That's enough.
來吧
Now!
它卡住了
It's stuck!
把它關上
Close it!
關不上
I can't!
好像少了個零件
I think there's a piece missing!
克萊莉
Clary!
我真的需要圣杯
I really need this.
媽媽
Mom?
-去找其他人  -好的
- Find the others. - All right.
你想去上面還是下面
All right, you want to take the upstairs or the down?
我不太喜歡地下室
I'm not too crazy about the basement.
我快擋不住它們了
I can't hold them back any longer!
西蒙  快點
Simon, hurry!
克萊莉
Clary!
你好呀  加洛維先生
Hello, Mr. Garroway.
看來你今天過得不怎樣啊
Looks like you're having a rough day, eh?
我想此時此刻最仁慈的
I guess the humane thing to do in this situation
就是結束你的生命
would be to put you down.
但是你不是想看我變身嗎
But you wanted to see me change.
是啊
I do.
起來
Get up!
兒子  你還想打多久
So, boy, how far do you want to take this?
打到最后一口氣
To the end.
西蒙
Simon!
伊莎貝爾
Isabelle!
靠著我
Lean on me.
離開這兒  快走
Get out! Go on!
快離開這兒
Get out of here.
走吧
Come on!
快走
Go!
有人跟我說你喜歡彈琴
Somebody told me that you like to play music.
約翰·巴赫肯定為你驕傲
Johann would be very proud.
你將死在拉杰爾的劍下
Now you shall die by Raziel's sword.
住手
Stop!
不然我把圣杯扔了
Or I'll drop it!
不要做傻事
You don't want to do that.
克萊莉  不要把圣杯給他
Don't give it to him, Clary.
你聽我說
I need you to listen to me.
作為你的父親
As your father,
我請求你
I'm begging you.
如果你真是個好父親
If you'd been a real dad,
你會懂我  你會知道圣杯在哪
you'd know me well enough to imagine where the Cup is,
你會知道我的內心將它置于何處
where my deepest thoughts are taking it.
你一點都不了解我
You don't know the first thing about me.
你不是我爸爸
You're not my dad...
永遠都不是
And you never will be.
我向你保證  你再也不會見到我
I promise, you'll never have to see me again.
謝謝你  克萊莉
Thank you, Clary.
沒有圣杯  我們會迷失
Without this Cup, we are lost.
不是我們
Not "We."
是你
You.
克萊莉
Clary!
-不要  不要放手  -我絕不放手
- No! Don't let go! - Never!
拿著這個
Here!
你還好吧
Are you okay?
我不知道
I don't know.
我明白你所做的一切
I understand why you did what you did.
我原諒你
And I forgive you.
我想告訴你
I want you to know,
我守住了你的秘密
your secret's safe with me.
-嗨  -你來了
-Hey. -Hey.
你媽媽怎么樣了
So, how's she doing?
還算穩定
Stable.
醫生也不知道她喝了什么
The doctors don't know what she took,
我們只能耐心等待
so we just have to wait.
對不起
I'm sorry.
我可能對待感情有些老土
I guess I'm an old romantic.
我總希望當我最終向對方表白時
I always hoped that when I finally said "I love you" to someone,
她能給我同樣的回應
she'd say the same thing back.
你會找到那個人的
And that someone will.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
你累了
Hey, you're tired.
去休息一下  我們照顧她
Go sleep, we'll take care of her.
-好的  -過來
- Yeah. - Come on.
Underneath the echoes
Buried in the shadows
To see your ghost
But you must know I'll be here waiting
Hoping Praying
That this light will guide you home
When you're feeling
lost I'll leave my love
房間收拾得不錯
I like what you've done with the place.
Hidden in the sun
我施了點小魔法
I've got a few tricks up my sleeve.
克萊莉  我們都擔心你不回來了
Clary, we're afraid you're not coming back.
For when the darkness comes
我現在很難待在你身邊
It's just really hard to be around you right now.
對我來說也很難
It's hard for me as well.
但這不只是關乎我倆
But this is about more than us.
你有驚人的天賦  我們需要你
You have an incredible gift, and we need you.
我需要你
I need you.
我不知道該怎么辦
I just don't know.
你記得我說過從沒見過天使嗎
Remember when I said I'd never seen an angel?
我說了謊
Well, I lied.
你仍然是我見過的最勇敢的凡人
You're still the bravest mundane I've ever met.
我不是凡人
I'm not a mundane.
等等  杰斯
Wait, Jace!
I'll be here waiting
Hoping Praying
你不必著急
You took your time.
That this light will guide you home
你剛剛說需要我
You said you needed me.
When you're feeling
你要好好保管它
You should keep that safe.
lost I'll leave my love
是的
Yeah.
我能不能...
Is it okay if I...
我可以...
Do I...
Hidden in the sun
-我能不能...-可以
- Is it okay if I... - Yeah.
For when the darkness comes
克萊莉  我不相信
Look, Clary, I don't believe it.
在我心里  我覺得那不是真的
It doesn't feel like the truth, not in my heart.
我只是不知道應該再如何看這個世界
I just don't know how to look at the world anymore.
我看不到街道  交通燈  汽車
I don't see streets and traffic lights and cars.
我看到惡魔和天使
I see demons and angels.
一切都不同了
Everything's different.
世界還是這個世界
The world's the same.
只是你不再是你了
You're the one who's different.
記不記得霍奇說的那句話
Don't you remember what Hodge said?
什么話
What?
所有的故事都是真的
All the stories are true.
For when the darkness comes